[{"answer": "This show is not where I want it to be right now.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Well, I'm going to ask Mr. Lauer which is more cutthroat, the race for the White House or the morning TV awards?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Am I going to get a word in here?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm thinking about what's changed.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "What are you -- what do you think -- I mean, it's like it's -- what are you literally --are you thinking about what I'm going to do with the kids this weekend or are you -- are already fashioned the show in your head?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "It doesn't and I do.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You're biting, you want -- so what would break the rules if Matt Lauer engaged?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Word association.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Word association?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Extraordinarily talented.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Katie Couric?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "AUER: Exactly the same guy off the air as he is on the air.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "How about that thug, Al Roker?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I'm just saying.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Too many kids on Ritalin, Matt?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Matt.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "But aren't there examples where it works?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "It's crazy.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "To come back at 25, how do you view it?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Let him keep going.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What's going through your mind at that moment?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Young ingenue.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "He's doing this just for the haircut?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "This is \"Today\" with Katie Couric and Matt Lauer.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Can you?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "You know, normally it's there.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "If you're going to pick one, the one that you go, you know what, how did I not ask that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "It did in the beginning.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Does it bother you?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I want to make it better.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "What do you want to do with the show different?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Lights a little bit of fire under our butts, there's no question about it.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "How does that change when you come to work in the morning?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Do you think both these guys get it?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Thank you very much, Donny.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How are you, doc?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I'll walk you through it, but if I walk you through it, I'm going to extend it to everybody who is watching right now.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What did we do?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Now your height is -- you're about five-ten?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Hundred.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Do you know how much the average sexual encounter burns off in calories?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "It involves all that.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Does -- what does that actually mean to reinvent the sexual relationship?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Most women have the equivalent of a G-spot.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "What is one thing a guy at home should take away from this?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "You have to excite that part of the female anatomy.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "They do?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "All human livers.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Doc, that's a human livers?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "This fatty liver -- having trouble with those gloves?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "I want to use one hand.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "What kind of doctor would you have been?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Bad liver.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "What does that cause?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "But when you have a liver that's turned to fat and making bad cholesterol, and that same belly fat is causing high blood pressure and problems with diabetes, you get a heart like this.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Isn't this stunning?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "Figure out the blood pressure issue.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Very quickly, if I want to get from that to the better heart, the five simple things to do?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "I'll give you the big button.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "Is there another button to push?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "I'm going to bring that home with me.", "docId": "120530pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "Want the heart?", "qSentId": 808}]